Joshua Gutierrez

josh.gvtie@gmail.com

5126306706

linkedin.com/in/joshua-gutierrez-588b1018a

https://www.joshuagutie.com

Summary

Diligent worker with 4 years of customer service experience and 3 years of dedicated practice in computer programming. Proficient in CSS, HTML, and Javascript, with a fundamental understanding of SQL. Dedication to the highest standards when helping costumers.

Experience



W team member

Whataburger

Aug 2022 - Present (1 month +)

Team member tasked with fast paced and exceptional quality work.

Laborer

Reliable Roofing & Repairs

Aug 2021 - May 2022 (10 months)

Working to install or repair roofs on residential or commercial structures, inspect roofs to check for any damage to the shingles, tiles, or waterproofing, and identify areas where repairs need to be made.

Certified Sterilization Technician

Walden Dental

Apr 2021 - Aug 2021 (5 months)

Tasked with cleaning rooms, setting up rooms, sterilizing all tools, and calibrating all dental equipment. Tasked with assisting in scheduling and seating patients. Excelled in calming patients with dental anxiety

Overnight Stocker

H-F-B

Jul 2019 - Present (3 years 2 months +)

Recognized to be within the top 3% of fastest stockers in the store. Led moral after much larger trucks were received due to Covid-19.

Team Member

Whataburger

Oct 2016 - Jul 2019 (2 years 10 months)

Assisted and managed orders from all customers. Proficient in both the kitchen and costumer service. Was awarded for both fastest order times and most positive surveys by costumers.

Education

Masters Learning Institute

High School Diploma, Computer Programming 2015 - 2019

Skills

Fast Learner • Problem Solving • User Experience (UX) • User Interface Design • Self Learning • Teamwork • Communication • Organization Skills • Team Motivation • Back-End Web Development